您应该事先想到这一点。
You should have thought of that beforehand.
一旦出门，这将是一个不好的记忆。
Once you're out it'll just be a bad memory.
耳环
A ear tee
GE
ge
Ge
erere =
Ere =
== = = 52 i =是串行sarai
== - = = 52 I= es slit ere ie Sarai serials
由西班牙人建造，哦，谁知道何时。
built by the Spanish, oh, who knows when.
r r对
Rm ri
的
ee
女士们，你晚了。
You are late, ladies.
永无止境的繁文tape节和文书工作。
Never-ending red tape and paperwork.
我不在乎！
I don't care!
这不是我的错。
It wasn't my fault.
我不得不等待文书工作。
I had to wait for the paperwork.
在这里，一切都是顺序的。
Here, it's all in order.
我们不应该带走一个女孩吗？
Aren't we supposed to take away a girl?
是的。
Yes.
带她过来。
Bring her over.
今天早上我们在她的牢房里找到了她。她死了。
We found her in her cell this morning. She was dead.
这很愚蠢。她知道她将在几天内被释放。
It's stupid. She knew she was going to be freed in a few days.
她总是害怕自由。
She always was scared of freedom.
自杀？
A suicide?
她的文书工作就在她旁边的棺材旁边。
Her paperwork's right next to her in the coffin.
由管理者签名并批准。
Signed and approved by the governer.
我再说一遍，下次您会准时在这里。
And I repeat, next time you will be here on time.
让新来者挺身而出。
Make the newcomers come forward for their instructions.
你的名字？
Your name?
-Nathalie Mendoza。 - 在这里您说“夫人”。
- Nathalie mendoza. - Here you say "madame."
你的电话号码？
Your number?
98，夫人。
98, madame.
- 你呢？ -97。
- What about you? - 97.
你以前去过这里。
You've been here before.
这次你在这里多长时间？
How long are you here for this time?
一年，夫人。
One year, madame.
这取决于您的行为。
That depends on your behavior.
否则，我将使您的假期持续更长的时间。
Otherwise I'll make your vacation last longer.
保持一件事。
Get one thing straight.
从现在开始，
Starting right now,
你没有个性。
you have no personality.
你什么都不是。
You are nothing.
你只不过是数字。
You are nothing but numbers.
忘记你存在。
Forget that you exist.
- 你好。 - 重新到达...
- Hello. - Anew arrival...
新来者在这个地狱中的分心是一个很好的分散注意力。
A newcomer's a nice distraction in this hellhole.
杰西卡！
Jessica!
后退？这次你在里什么？
Back? What are you in for this time?
什么问题。
What a question.
同样旧。我不背叛原因。
Same old. I don't betray the cause.
helga！
Helga!
她生病了。
She's sick.
WHO？纳塔莉？
Who? Nathalie?
是的。 98号
Yes. Number 98
她很好。不要全力以赴。
she's fine. don't get all worked up.
当然，她不感到热。
Of course she's not feeling hot.
她需要修复。
She needs a fix.
警察把她钉在船上。
The cops nailed her on a boat.
她没有票，但没有足够的海洛因来满足成瘾者。
She was riding with no ticket but with enough heroin to satisfy an army of addicts.
有人不能帮她吗？
Can't anyone help her?
她正在接受特殊的家庭治疗。
She's getting the special house treatment.
她要去冷火鸡。
She's going cold Turkey.
现在还可以。
For now it's ok.
完成后，她将失去所有的头发。
Once they're done, she'll lose all her hair.
来吧，躺下孩子。
Come on, lie down kid.
放松。你必须睡觉。
Relax. You've got to sleep.
您无论如何都不能做任何事情。
You can't do anything anyhow.
哦，别哭。
Oh, don't cry.
说，我曾经告诉过你为什么我在这里吗？
Say, did I ever tell you why I'm in here?
不，为什么？
No. Why?
这不是秘密。
It's no secret.
卖淫。我操了一个我不应该有的家伙。
Prostitution. I fucked a fella I shouldn't have.
你呢？
How about you?
我敢打赌，你想着一些非常疯狂的东西。
I bet you're in for something pretty wild.
来吧，不要哭。
Come on, don't cry.
我要进入那个羽毛床。
I'm gonna get in that featherbed.
州长，我希望你很开心。
Governor, I hope you were entertained.
哦，那个白色的天使。
Oh, that white angel.
他很兴奋。
He was ravishing.
我知道你会喜欢他。
I knew you would like him.
还有新的被拘留者？
And the new detainees?
他们中间有一个小小的金发...
There's a little blond among them...
编号99。
Number 99.
年轻的，
Young,
令人兴奋，身体很好。
exciting, with a nice body.
我认为您可能宁愿喜欢她。
I think you might rather like her.
我稍后再见。
I'll see about her later.
我今天有很多工作。
I have a lot of work today.
谢谢您这么快的州长。
Thank you for coming so quickly governor.
我一如既往地致力于你。
I am, as always devoted, to you.
你太好了。
You're too kind.
很快，您将能够证明自己的奉献精神。
And very soon you will be able to prove your devotion.
您非常了解我喜欢对待我的奉献者。
You know very well how I like to treat my devotees.
你说99？
You said 99?
是的。
Yes.
好吧
Alright
但是要谨慎。
but proceed with caution.
有人告诉我，死去的女孩的背部深深地疤痕。
The dead girl, I'm told, has deep scars all over her back.
我坚持所有被拘留者都接受纪律和劳动。
I insist all detainees submit to discipline and labor.
但是我们有一个新司法部长
But we have a new justice minister
而且他注定要热心。
and he is bound to be zealous.
您一定不能忘记这是今年第二次死亡。
You mustn't forget this is the second death this year.
是的，是的，我知道。所以呢？
Yes, yes, I know. So what?
我们必须避免麻烦。
We must avoid trouble.
总督，麻烦就是我整天的全天。
Trouble is all I have all day long, governor.
我习惯了麻烦。
I'm used to trouble.
编号99 ...
Number 99...
我必须先看囚犯。
I must first see to prisoners.
危险，残酷的男人。
Dangerous, brutal men.
我们什么时候再次见面？
When shall we see each other again?
也许明天。
Tomorrow perhaps.
我会记得看...
I will remember to take a look at...
编号99。
Number 99.
所以直到明天...
So until tomorrow...
这将带来极大的荣幸。
It will be with great pleasure.
什么？这是什么？
What? What is it?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
没有什么。
Nothing.
你有一场噩梦。
You had a nightmare.
- 谁哭了？ - 纳塔莉（Nathalie）。
- Who was it that cried out? - Nathalie.
她病得很重。
She is seriously ill.
哦...来吧！睡觉。
Oh... come on! Go to sleep.
这不是让她生病的毒品。
It's not the drugs making her sick.
你知道什么？你是医生吗？
What do you know? Are you a doctor?
不，我只有一种感觉。
No, I just have a feeling.
您认为我们应该做什么？
What do you think we should do?
我们应该打电话给警卫。让她叫医生。
We should call a guard. Make her call a doctor.
警卫！
Guard!
你会闭嘴吗？
Will you shut up?
编号99。
Number 99.
99！
Number 99!
是的，夫人。
Yes, madame.
对不服从的惩罚，
The punishment for insubordination,
您会学到的，在洞中8天。
you will learn, is 8 days in the hole.
纳塔莉很狡猾。
Nathalie is delirious.
她要死了。
She's going to die.
以及拒绝服从董事的惩罚
And the punishment for refusing to obey the director
在孔中为15天。
is 15 days in the hole.
我希望你已经理解了！
I hope you have understood!
你好，医生。
Hello, doctor.
那很快。
That was quick.
她已经死了。
She was already dead.
几乎总是如此。
That's how it almost always is.
这个女人成为导演多久了？
How long has this woman been the director?
哦，一定已经十年了。
Oh, it must be 10 years already.
她曾经是一名警卫。
She used to be a guard.
没有人离开那个地方。
No one ever leaves that place.
我们会看到的。
We'll see about that.
快点！
Faster!
否则您将在洞中获得几天的时间。快点！
Or you'll get days in the hole. Faster!
您的句子多长时间？
How long is your sentence?
十五个月。要长。
Fifteen months. It's going to be long.
你呢？
How about you?
相同的。这是我的第一句话。
Same. It's my first sentence.
我去过这里呆了十天。
I've been here for ten days.
你能接受吗？
Can you take it?
这不是我介意的工作。
It's not the work I mind.
嘿，公主，想念你在走路的那些街道吗？
Hey, Princess, miss those streets you were walking?
关闭陷阱，否则可能会生锈。
Shut your trap or it might rust.
那是没有办法为妓女说话。
That's no way to talk for a hooker.
停止它。你疯了！
Stop it. You're crazy!
停止！
Stop!
你们两个，跟我来。
You two, come with me.
其余的人，继续工作。
The rest of you, keep working.
他们会发生什么？
What's gonna happen to them?
他们会对他们做什么？
What'll they do to them?
这将是一个聚会。
It'll be a party.
晚上好。
Good evening.
像往常一样准时。
On time, as usual.
我今天不是你的第一个访客？
I am not your first visitor today?
不。
No.
医生已经到今天早上了。
The doctor has been by this morning.
其中一个是...
One of the girls is...
死的。我知道。
Dead. I know.
我怎么知道这不是一个行为？
How could I have known it wasn't an act?
哦，那不是责备。
Oh, that was not a reproach.
我不是新司法部长。
I am not the new justice minister.
今晚很热。
It's hot tonight.
医生说，将向部长发送报告。
The doctor said a report would be sent to the minister.
好吧，我们在那里。
Well, there we are.
正是我一直担心的。
Just what I have been fearing.
但是部长的工作应仅限于寻找负责犯罪的人。
But the minister's job should be limited to finding those responsible for crimes.
这些是可以解决的问题。
These are matters that can be solved.
我会给你你的酒。
I'll get you your glass of wine.
让我们谈谈更多令人愉快的事情。
Let's talk about more pleasant matters.
数字997如何？
How is number 997?
你知道，亲爱的，你种了种子。
You know, you planted that seed, my dear.
她与另一个女孩打架。
She got in a fight with another girl.
我不得不相应地惩罚她。
I had to punish her accordingly.
谁是另一个女孩？
Who was the other girl?
numbr 76你知道那个。
Numbr 76-you know the one.
是的，你知道她。
Yes, you know her.
她是一年来这里的人。
She's the one that's been here for a year.
啊，是的。佐伊。
Ah yes. Zoe.
她受伤了。
She's injured.
她被锁在医务室。
She's locked up in the infirmary.
和她亲爱的朋友99。
With her dear friend 99.
他们会呆在那里，直到他们化妆。
They'll stay there until they've made up.
好吧，他们必须受到州长的惩罚。
Well, they must be punished governor.
惩罚的选择，我会留给你。
The choice of punishment, I will leave to you.
真的吗？
Really?
我真的认为您错过了您的电话，Thelma。
I really think you missed your calling, Thelma.
我可以看到你是一个经营妓院的夫人。
I can see you as a madame running a brothel.
不，州长。
No, governor.
你很清楚我在这里找到了我的真实职业
You know very well that I have found my true vocation here
而且我奉献自己，身体和灵魂。
and that I am devoting myself to it, body and soul.
的确。
Indeed.
你要停止呼唤吗？
Are you going to stop bawling?
足够的！你听到了吗？
Enough! Do you hear?
这是毫无意义的。
It's pointless.
别哭了。
Stop crying.
是因为你和那个妓女
It's because of you and that whore
我的腿都被刮了。
that my leg is all scraped up.
我不是在哭。
And I'm not crying.
你听到了吗？我从未哭过。
Do you hear? I have never cried.
快点。这里。
Come on. Here.
来吧，我说。
Come on, I said.
不！请别打扰我！
No! Leave me alone!
好吧，好吧。
Well, well.
两个老朋友。
Two old friends.
我的两个看起来好像没有相处的朋友。
My two friends who looked like they didn't get along.
没关系，我的天使。
That's alright, my angels.
有时很难区分爱与仇恨。
Sometimes it's hard to distinguish between love and hate.
他们可以很好地同居。
They can cohabit so well.
一段时间以来，有关该主题的更多信息。
More on that subject in a little while.
这里太热了。
It's so hot in here.
窒息。
Stifling.
我们会变得更舒适吗？
Shall we get a little more comfortable?
请别打扰我！
Leave me alone!
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
玛格达。
Magda.
我住了六个月。你相信吗？
I'm in for six months. Can you believe it?
太久了。
That's so long.
在这个地狱洞中，六个月是永恒的。
In this hell hole six months is an eternity.
你呢？你有多长时间？
How about you? How long do you have?
我不知道。
I don't know.
您的情况是有条件的吗？
Your case is conditional?
你可怜的东西。那是最糟糕的。
You poor thing. That's the worst.
您可能永远不会出去。
You'll probably never get out.
那是不可能的。
That's not possible.
哦，你知道，
Oh, you know,
我没什么意思。
I didn't mean anything by that.
你的论文？
Your papers?
这是一封信。
This is a letter.
对不起。这就是我所拥有的。
I'm sorry. Itis all I have.
它是给导演的。
It's addressed to the director.
你好。
Hello.
导演迪亚兹。
Director Diaz.
而且你是...
And you are...
导演卡罗尔。
Director Carole.
还没有。
Not yet.
部长的信已经足够清楚。
The minister's letter is clear enough.
是的，
Yes,
它说一个月...
it says for one month...
形成意见所需的时间。
The time it takes to form an opinion.
我知道这意味着什么。
I know what this means.
我必须离开。我明白。
I must leave. I understand.
那取决于你。
That depends on you.
但是我希望你留下来
But I would prefer you stayed
并帮助我。
and helped me.
帮你吗？
Helped you?
是的。
Yes.
我敢肯定我会需要你的。
I'm certain I will need you.
您在监狱管理方面有任何经验吗？
Do you have any experience in prison management?
很少。
Very little.
我已经处理了少年犯罪。
I have dealt with juvenile delinquents.
这是我第一次在监狱中。
This is my first time in a penitentiary.
您有很多要学习的东西。
You have a great deal to learn.
我知道。
I know.
这就是为什么我要你帮助我。
That is why I would ask you to help me.
我可以向您保证，如果您想检查一下
I can assure you that if you wish to check up on things
您可以看到所有文件，收据，
you can see all the files, the receipts,
和帐户是有序的。
and accounts are in order.
我们有99名被拘留者
We have 99 detainees
截至今天早上的滚动电话。
as of this morning's roll call.
但是我相信你，夫人。
But I trust you, madame.
我想参观房屋。
I would like to visit the premises.
你会陪我吗？
Will you accompany me?
她认为她到底是谁？
Who the hell does she think she is?
沉默！
Silence!
嘿！
Hey!
你为什么停止工作？
Why have you stopped working?
继续！
Carry on!
那里面有什么？
And what is in there?
那就是洞。
That's the hole.
现在有人在那里吗？
Anyone in there right now?
是的。那里有一个被拘留者。
Yes. There's one detainee in there.
出于什么原因？
For what reason?
试图唤醒他人和不服从。
Attempt to awaken others, and insubordination.
她去过那里多久了？
And how long has she been there?
明天将是一个星期。
It'll be a week tomorrow.
我想见她。
I'd like to see her.
你会失望的。
You'll be disappointed.
很好。如您所愿。
Very well. As you wish.
起来！来吧，站起来！
Stand up! Come on, stand!
站起来走路。快点！
Stand up and walk. Come on!
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
99.
告诉我你的名字。
Tell me your name.
在这里被拘留者没有名字。
Here detainees have no names.
请告诉我你的名字。
Please tell me your name.
你叫什么名字？
What is your name?
玛丽。
Marie.
谢谢，玛丽。
Thank you, Marie.
把她带回其他人。
Take her back to the others.
她的惩罚是两个星期。
Her punishment is two weeks long.
我想和这个女孩说话。
I would like to talk to this girl.
一对一。
One on one.
桑托斯州长，小姐Carole。
Governor Santos, mademoiselle Carole.
我已经了解了部长的信。
I have learned of the minister's letter.
我也有一封信给你。
I also have a letter to give to you.
请夫人，您能为我准备一个房间吗？
Please madame, could you kindly have a room prepared for me?
是的，很高兴。
Yes, gladly.
所以你是Leonie Carole？
So you are leonie Carole?
是的。
Yes.
我叫桑托斯。我是州长，因此您的上司。
My name is Santos. I am the governor, hence your superior.
部长确实告诉了我。
The minister did inform me of it.
他想收到每日报告。
He would like to receive a daily report.
自然。
Naturally.
但是您必须给我发送一份副本。
But you must send me a copy of it.
坐下。
Sit down.
您应该知道，我对您被发送到这里并不感到惊讶。
You should know, I'm not surprised that you've been sent here.
我懂了。
I see.
这里发生了可怕的事情。
Terrible things have happened here.
导演迪亚兹夫人有点过失。
Madame Diaz, the director, has been a little too negligent.
我一直告诉她：“你努力工作，但你太多了。”
I keep telling her, "you work hard but there's too much that gets by you."
是的。
Yes.
她应该辞职。
She should resign.
我要求她待更长的时间
I have asked her to stay on a little longer
我懂了。
I see.
你是一个战术思想家。
You're something of a tactical thinker.
我会容纳你。我确定我们会相处的。
I'll accommodate you. I'm sure we'll get along.
我敢肯定。
Of that, I am certain.
您应该解决。
You should get settled.
让我了解这里发生的一切。
Keep me abreast of everything that goes on here.
我希望一切都会顺利进行，州长。
I hope everything will go well, governor.
一个建议，小姐Carole，
One piece of advice, mademoiselle Carole,
您必须尊重秩序和纪律的严格性。
you must respect the strictness of order and discipline.
如果通过弱点，您对这些女孩的丝毫丝毫
If, through weakness, you concede the slightest thing to these girls
您将不再拥有任何权威。
you will no longer have any authority.
请记住，Carole小姐。
Remember that, mademoiselle Carole.
再见，州长。
Goodbye, governor.
我相信我们很快会再次见面。
I am sure we will see each other again soon.
我也是。
So am I.
我不吓到你，对吗？
I don't scare you, do I?
不，别管我。
No. Leave me alone.
我为你感到。
I feel for you.
他们真的把你操了。
They really fucked you up.
就像你在乎。
Like you care.
你知道，有一段时间，我也有像你这样的愿望。
You know, there was a time, I too had aspirations like you.
我是舞者。
I was a dancer.
我发誓，一个奇妙的生活，
A marvelous life, I swear,
以及有史以来最好的工作。
and the best job ever.
每个人都认识我。
Everyone knew me.
我拥有了。
I had it all.
这些人都在追我。
The men were all after me.
它可能持续了，但是老板嫉妒我。
It could have lasted, but the boss was jealous of me.
摘下！
Take it off!
为什么？它打扰你吗？
Why? Does it bother you?
一天晚上，我遇到了一个男人。
One night, I met a man.
我为他疯狂。
I was crazy about him.
我不知道她在看我们。
I didn't know she was watching us.
晚上好，佐伊。
Good evening, Zoe.
卡拉。
Carla.
妓女！
Whore!
那真是可怕的佐伊。
That's terrible Zoe.
她怎么把你赶出了洞？
How come she got you out of the hole?
我不知道。
I don't know.
她不像其他人。她与众不同。
She's not like the others. She's different.
提防。
Watch out.
她可能比bit子更糟。
She might be worse than the bitch.
当心。她出去了。
Be careful. She's out for something.
我今天早上见到她，她似乎还可以。
I saw her this morning and she seemed ok.
您应该问她她是怎么来这里的。
You should have asked her how she ended up here.
通常只是旧的巫婆。
It's usually just old hags here.
你为什么不问她？
Why don't you ask her?
99号。跟我来。
Number 99. Come with me.
好吧，好吧。
Well, well.
离开我们。
Leave us.
坐下，玛丽。
Sit down, Marie.
你为什么受到惩罚？你做了什么？
Why were you punished? What had you done?
因为我呼吁帮助。
Because I called out for help.
为什么？
Why?
其中一个女孩病了。她需要一名医生。
One of the girls was sick. She needed a doctor.
医生来了吗？
Did a doctor come?
我不知道。
I don't know.
女孩在哪里？
Where is the girl?
她死了。
She's dead.
你来这里多久了？
How long have you been here?
七天。
Seven days.
自从您到达以来，您一直在洞中？
And you've been in the hole ever since you arrived?
你为什么在这里？你做了什么？
Why are you here? What have you done?
告诉我。
Tell me.
我研究了您的文件。
I have studied your file.
我学到了很多。
I haven't learned very much.
我想了解您在这里的最终结果。
I'd like to understand how you ended up here.
现在来。冷静下来。
Come now. Calm down.
那么，发生了什么事？
So, what happened?
告诉我。
Tell me.
尝试。
Try.
那天晚上，我在等公共汽车。
That night I was waiting for the bus.
一个骑摩托车的男人为我提供了骑车。
A man on a motorbike offered me a ride.
我和他一起去。
I went with him.
天黑了
It was dark
而且我不知道该地区。
and I didn't know the area.
他带我去了很多。
He took me to a dirt lot.
总共有四个人...
There were four men in all...
可怕的野蛮人。
Horrible brutes.
他们攻击了我。
They attacked me.
如何，怎么样。
Come, come.
其中一个有刀。
One of them had a knife.
我试图从他那里拿走它。
I tried to take it from him.
突然我意识到，我被鲜血覆盖。
Suddenly I realized,I was covered in blood.
你杀了他。
You killed him.
不！不！
No! No!
法院仍然认为您有罪。
Still the court found you guilty.
没有人相信我。我说实话。
No one believes me. I'm telling the truth.
我认为发生的是您正在转动技巧
What I think happened is that you were turning tricks
当其中一名男子拒绝向您付钱时，您要问的钱
and when one of the men refused to pay you the money you were asking
你战斗，愤怒地杀了他。
you fought and in a rage you killed him.
不，为什么没有人相信我？
No, why won't anyone believe me?
好的。
All right.
现在我相信你。
Now I do believe you.
但是记住这一点。
But remember this.
所有受到谴责，自称是无辜的人。
All those who are condemned, claim to be innocent.
很少有人说实话。
Very few are telling the truth.
我会要求您的文件发送给我。
I will ask for your file to be sent to me.
不过，逆转的机会很小。
Though, the chances of a reversal are very slim.
现在回到您的牢房。
Go back to your cell now.
谢谢你，夫人。
Thank you, madame.
这个Leonie Carole并不像您首先想到的那样愚蠢。
This leonie Carole is not as stupid as you had first thought.
我从没想过她很愚蠢。
I never thought her stupid.
我认为她很聪明
I think she's very clever
而且她在这里不是要解雇微不足道的监狱董事，而是你。
and that she's here not to fire an insignificant prison director, but rather, you.
我？那太荒谬了。
Me? That's absurd.
部长对我完全有信心。
The minister has complete confidence in me.
你确定吗？
Are you sure of that?
是的，我有声誉。
Yes, I have a reputation.
真的吗？
Really?
我们需要防止她可能造成的伤害。
We need to prevent the harm she might do.
想想她将发送的报告。
Think of the reports she will send.
你说得对。我们必须采取行动。
You're right. We must act.
为时已晚。
Before it's too late.
在她向他发送报告之前，他将收到我们的报告。
Before she's sent him her report, he will receive our report on her.
好主意。我们必须在此问题上积极主动。
Good idea. We must be proactive in this matter.
绝对地。
Absolutely.
但是我们能发现什么反对她？
But what can we find against her?
我注意到了
I have noticed
她试图获得某些被拘留者的信任。
that she tries hard to gain the trust of certain detainees.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
她可能对其中一个女孩感兴趣
Might she be interested in one of these girls
而不是你，州长？
instead of you, governor?
什么？
What?
多么好主意。
What a great idea.
让我们不要浪费时间。
Let's not waste any time.
给我姓名，详细信息，事实，我想要所有的细节。
Give me names, details, facts, I want all the saucy details.
哦，我会给你。
Oh, I will give them to you.
简而言之，州长，
In a nutshell, governor,
她爱上了99号。
she's in love with number 99.
快点！
Faster!
快来！
Come on now!
看！
Look!
- 胡安·迭戈！ - 你知道那个家伙吗？
- Juan Diego! - You know that guy?
是的。
Yes.
我必须和他说话。
I have to talk to him.
等等，我有一个主意。
Wait, I have an idea.
打败它。
Beat it.
去！快的。
Go! Quick.
赦免我，但我需要和你说话。
Pardon me, but I need to talk to you.
最后！
Finally!
我试图告诉你。
I tried to get word to you.
我想告诉你我还好。
I wanted to tell you I was ok.
- 这是什么？ - 什么都没有...只是划痕。
- What's this? - Nothing... just a scratch.
听，
Listen,
在岛的另一端
at the other end of the island
有一个渔民村。
there's a village of fishermen.
他们有船。
They have boats.
十天后，在新月，
In ten days, at the new moon,
一个朋友和我要逃脱。
a friend and I are going to escape.
但是胡安，我在哪里可以找到你？
But Juan, where will I find you?
距离村庄有两个港口。
Two kilometers from the village there's a port.
我们将在黎明时在那里等您。
We'll wait for you there, at daybreak.
哦，罗莎莉。
Oh, Rosalie.
当心。
Be careful.
土壤
Zoel
什么玛丽？你想要什么？
what Marie? What do you want?
你为什么不睡觉，梦见你的新女朋友？
Why don't you go to sleep and dream of your new girlfriend?
她永远不会让你离开这里。
She'll never get you out of here.
您可以确定。
You can be sure of that.
她会和你一起睡几次
She'll sleep with you several times
然后让你在这里腐烂。
and then leave you to rot here.
给你的信。
A letter for you.
谢谢。
Thank you.
被拘留者想紧急与您交谈。
A detainee wants to speak to you urgently.
哪一个？
Which one?
编号99。
Number 99.
我饿了。
I'm hungry.
我也是。
Me too.
您为什么不要求Mercy姐妹在这里做一些有关食物的事情？
Why don't you ask sister mercy to do something about the food here?
我只见过她两次。
I've only seen her twice.
她会同意您的要求。你是她的宠物。
She'll agree to whatever you ask. You're her pet.
哦，闭嘴。
Oh, shut up.
您介意您的嘴并远离此。
You mind your mouth and stay out of this.
我知道你不挖女孩。
I know you don't dig girls.
妓女！你的垃圾！
Whore! You piece of trash!
荡妇！
Slut!
我会告诉你！
I'll show youl!
这是怎么回事？
What's going on here?
足够的！你听到我的声音吗？
Enough! Do you hear me?
停止！
Stop!
你知道你应得的吗？
You know what you deserve?
发生了什么？
What happened?
他们战斗。
They fought.
数字97和数字76。
Number 97 and number 76.
我可以看到。
I can see that.
面包和水只持续两天。
Bread and water only for two days.
他们每个人都会在洞中进行7天。
They'll each do seven days in the hole.
不，不是洞。
No. Not the hole.
这种惩罚已被消除。
That punishment has been eliminated.
你好。
Hello.
玛丽，你为什么要见我？
Why did you ask to see me, Marie?
这是什么？
What is it?
我想知道您是否发现了有关我的案子的新事物。
I wanted to know if you had found out anything new about my case.
是的。
Yes.
对不起，我无能为力。我收到答案。
I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do. I received an answer.
您的情况很清楚。没有机会进行审查。
Your case is clear. There's no chance for a review.
给我看信。
Show me the letter.
我摧毁了它。
I destroyed it.
我不相信你。
I don't believe you.
你是什​​么意思？
What do you mean?
你们都知道他们都在说什么吗？
Do you know what they all say?
您无所事事地帮助我离开这里。
You'll do nothing to help me get out of here.
玛丽，为什么我无能为力？
Marie, why would I do nothing to help?
显然，首先我必须和你一起睡觉。
Apparently first I'd have to sleep with you.
就像其他人一样，你是个bit子。
You're a bitch, just like the others.
你真令人恶心。
You're disgusting.
所以，小。
So, chiquita.
我什么时候可以离开这里？
When can I get out of here?
也许很快。我看到它来了。
Maybe soon. I see it coming.
你是什​​么意思？
What do you mean?
我们的好天使已经下达了命令。
Our good angel has given orders.
不再有夜间手表。
No more night watches.
我有一个好主意，
I have a great idea,
但是我们需要三个。
but we would need to have three.
我们需要罗莎莉，
We'd need Rosalie,
我...
me...
你呢。
And you.
这并不容易。距丛林30公里。
It won't be easy. It's 30 kilometers into the jungle.
如果我们不这样做，
And if we don't make it,
我们将被皇家搞砸。
We'll be royally screwed.
我不在乎。
I don't care.
所以你进去了吗？
So you're in?
我在里面。
I'm in.
这里。
Here.
拿钥匙。
Take the keys.
我必须告知您一个新规则有效。
I must inform you a new rule is in effect.
如果晚上被拘留者生病，
If during the night a detainee is sick,
你必须敲钟。
you must ring the bell.
但是，如果您没有充分理由打扰警卫，
But if you disturb the guards without good reason,
你会受到惩罚。
you'll be punished.
我感觉不好！
I don't feel good!
我很恶心。
I am so sick.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我病了。
I'm sick.
一举一动，我会割你的喉咙！
One move and I'll slit your throat!
我不会做到。
I won't make it.
罗莎莉，请。尝试挂在那里。
Rosalie, please. Try to hang in there.
我们现在不能停止。我们不能呆在这里！
We can't stop now. We can't stay here!
勇敢。
Be brave.
艰难的部分结束了。
The hard part's over.
你听到了吗？
Do you hear that?
警报器。
The sirens.
他们意识到我们走了。
They've realized we're gone.
来吧，快点！
Come on, hurry!
那些bit子。我认为他们警告了男士的监狱！
Those bitches. I think they alerted the men's penitentiary!
快来吧，迅速！
Come on, quickly!
嘿！多么的水果蛋糕。
Hey! What a fruitcake.
直接从丛林中。
Straight from the jungle.
水果蛋糕？
Fruitcake?
看起来我们使用同一裁缝。
Looks like we use the same tailor.
看！
Look!
你什么时候逃脱的？
When did you escape?
今晨。
This morning.
胡安迭戈在哪里？
Where is Juan Diego?
快点。来这里。
Come on. Come here.
你是罗莎莉吗？
Are you Rosalie?
是的，我是罗莎莉。
Yes, I'm Rosalie.
胡安·迭戈在哪里？我打算见他。
Where's Juan Diego? I'd planned to meet him.
他给了我这个。
He gave me this.
是你的。
It's yours.
是的。这是怎么回事？
Yes, it is. What's going on?
当他们看到我们逃脱时，警卫射击了胡安·迭戈。
The guards shot Juan Diego when they saw us escape.
哦，胡安！
Oh, Juan!
现在他们在你的路上。
Now they're on your trail.
逃脱时，我们将要上班。
We were going to work when we escaped.
那是胡安...
That's when Juan...
稍后我会感谢您的所作所为。
I'll thank you later for what you've done.
告诉我，你知道丛林吗？
Tell me, do you know the jungle?
不。
No.
但是大海应该直接向前。
But the sea should be straight ahead.
我们会更好地坚持在一起。
We'd do better to stick together.
如果我们没有迅速地进行地面，我们就会完成。
If we don't make ground quickly we're done for.
我们该怎么办，我们应该...
What should we do, we should...
我们应该沿着河流下来。
We should follow the river down.
它一定会通向大海。
It's bound to lead to the sea.
大海在哪里？
Where's the sea?
让我们前往山上。我们会找到它。
Let's head toward the mountains. We'll find it.
那不会导致我们进入印章
That won't lead us to the seal
你还有另一个建议吗？
do you have another suggestion?
我们会按他说的那样做。
We'll do as he says.
我们走吧。迅速地！
Let's go. Quickly!
他们深入丛林。
They're going deep into the jungle.
他们不会在山上找到我们。
They won't find us in the mountains.
不，我不会做到！
No, I'm not gonna make it!
是的，你会的！
Yes, you will!
快点。
Come on.
不，罗莎莉，请停下来。
No, Rosalie, please stop.
勇敢。
Be brave.
你和胡安就像兄弟，对吗？
You and Juan were like brothers, right?
你可以这么说。
You could say that.
像两个兄弟。
Like two brothers.
他曾经谈论过我吗？
Did he ever talk about me?
经常。
Often.
他总是说你是
He always said you were
世界上最好的女孩。
the nicest girl in the world.
当他去世时
And when he died,
他叫我的名字了吗？
did he call out my name?
是的，他做到了。
Yes, he did.
他告诉我要亲吻你，并为罗莎莉说了这句话。
He told me to kiss you and said this one's for Rosalie.
他说：“里卡多，对她好。
And he said, "Ricardo, be nice to her.
她是一个很棒的女孩。照顾她。”
She's a great gal. Take care of her."
我爱他。
I loved him.
我也是。
So did I.
他是个好人。
He was a great guy.
我也永远不会忘记他。
I'm never going to forget him either.
哦，胡安，我的爱。
Oh, Juan, my love.
我非常爱你。
I loved you so much.
哦，罗莎莉，你真漂亮。
Oh, Rosalie, you're so beautiful.
来吧，起床。
Come on, get up.
让我们继续前进。
Let's keep going.
十分钟休息。
Ten minute break.
弗雷迪！是我，里卡多！
Freddy! It's me, Ricardo!
你想要什么？
What do you want?
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
你在开玩笑，对吗？我们四个人。
You're kidding, right? There's four of us.
这里。
Here.
快速，让我们在这里离开。
Quick, let's get outta here.
一切好吗？
Everything okay?
是的。
Yes.
继续前进。我会照顾好这个。
Keep going. I'll take care of this.
不那么快。
Not so fast.
别管他们。他们刚逃脱了。
Leave them alone. They've just escaped.
我被谴责
I'm condemned to life
自从我看到一个女人已经好几年了！
and it's been years since I saw a woman!
里卡多哭了。
That was Ricardo crying out.
我们必须去他的营救。
We have to go to his rescue.
如果您想帮助他，请继续！
If you want to help him, go ahead!
那些野蛮人，他们得到了她。
Those brutes, they got her.
太糟糕了。我们会发生什么？
It's awful. What's going to happen to us?
我不知道，但是我们不能呆在这里！
I don't know, but we can't stay here!
快点！
Come on!
我们会碰到。
We'll run across.
如果他们看到我们怎么办？
What if they see us?
我们必须抓住机会。
We'll have to take our chances.
我的天使在哪里急忙？
Where to in such a hurry, my angels?
您的不耐烦使您更加理想。
Your impatience makes you even more desirable.
好的。我们明天再开始。
All right. We'll start again tomorrow.
解开他们！
Untie them!
您不认为他们受到了足够的惩罚吗？
Don't you think they've been punished enough?
我知道我该怎么办。对逃生者进行了制裁。
I know what I have to do. Sanctions are in place against the escapees.
规则是严格的，您必须识别它们。
The rules are strict and you must recognize them.
他们每天将在洞中花四个小时。
They will spend four hours each day in the hole.
可以每24小时服用体罚。
Corporal punishment can be administered every 24 hours.
这些是规则。
These are the rules.
可以每24小时进行一次体罚。
Corporal punishment can be administered every 24 hours and it will be.
拒绝司法部长！
Leave out the justice minister!
我在这里负责法律
I am responsible for the laws here
他们将受到尊重。
and they will be respected.
明天我们将检查所有被拘留者。
Tomorrow we'll have an inspection of all detainees.
那我会做出决定。
I'll make my decisions then.
我也很高兴明天再见。
I will also have the pleasure of seeing you again tomorrow.